...I'm a bit of a self-taught expert.
Howard, if I were to ask Leslie Winkle out,
it would just be for dinner.
I'm not gonna walk into the lab,
ask her to strip naked and dance for me.
(Howard:)Oh, then you're probably okay.
- Hello, Leslie.
- Hi, Leonard.
- I'd like to propose an experiment...
- Goggles.
(Howard:)Right.
(Leonard:)- I would like to propose an experiment.
- Hang on.
(Lesley:)I'm trying to see how long it takes
a 500-kilowatt oxygen-iodine laser...
...to heat up my cup of noodles.
(Leonard:)I've done it.
About two seconds, 2.6 for minestrone.
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
(Leonard:)Anyway, I was thinking more
of a biosocial exploration...
(Leonard:)...with a neurochemical overlay.
(Lesley:)Wait, are you asking me out?
I was going to characterize it
as the modification...
(Leonard:)...of our colleague/friendship paradigm
with the addition of a date-like component.